<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Chinese Classes</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>CACC Chinese School offers Chinese language courses mainly for two different groups of students, grades K-8 and high school students. The courses for K-8 students are designed for students who learn Chinese as a heritage language. These Chinese-as-a-heritage-language courses are in two different learning channels based on the textbooks used, one is the textbook entitled Chinese published by Jinan University, and the other one is the textbook entitled Stanford Chinese by Ma Liping; the high school courses are credit courses and non-credit courses. We currently offer three levels of high school credit courses, i.e. Chinese III, Chinese IV and AP Chinese Language and Culture. To enter a credit class, a student needs to take a placement test for proper placement. Non-credit courses include the Chinese III Prep Course and Chinese AP Prep. Any student with a need of preparation for entering the Chinese III class should take this Chinese III Prep Course first and, upon successfully completing the learning tasks in CLASS III course, will be allowed to take Chinese III. Chinese AP Prep course, as a non-credit course, does not require a placement test. Chinese as a Second Language courses are designed as a supplement outside of the above system for students who have no background of any kind in the Chinese language. A special note: The level of the Chinese III course represents a third year of taking Chinese as a foreign language, which means, UC/CSU recognize three years of a foreign language study for those students who have successfully completed Chinese III. For exactly the same reason, Chinese IV represents four years and AP Chinese represents a fifth year of taking a foreign language course in high school.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese Pre-Kindergarten (中文班 PK)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Pre-K class is designed for kids from 4 years old and up (birthday was on or before 8/18/2021). The period is children's beginning step to systematic training in language, so it's of vital importance to their future interest in learning Chinese. The teaching objectives for Pre-K are to develop language skills in listening, speaking, and the ability to recognize sight words through rhymes, songs, stories, games, and puzzles. Through a variety of fun and interesting activities, the teacher will stimulate children's natural curiosity and genuine interest in language learning. Meanwhile, Chinese language basics such as characters, strokes, and radicals are also emphasized through abundant exercises. And it includes themes such as daily life skills, five senses, animals, and colors. The popular Chinese and American holidays of the year are integrated into the teaching.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese Kindergarten (中文班 K)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Chinese Kindergarten is designed for children from 5 to 6 years old (birthday was on or before 8/18/2020). After a year's study, the kindergarten children will be able to read aloud or recite the nursery rhymes taught in class as well as to identify and read pinyin, thus laying a solid foundation for the first grade language study. The teaching is focused on learning popular Chinese nursery songs and daily oral expressions. Children are able to develop the sense of language and the ability for word recognition through reading the rhyming children's songs. Listening and speaking skills are also reinforced by learning fundamental characters and using simple sentences structures. Through a combination of effective teaching strategies by using teaching aids like pictures, real objects, crafts, stories and songs, the teacher achieves direct visual and hearing effects in teaching the students, therefore stimulating and maintaining their interest and enthusiasm in Chinese. Textbook: Mei Zhou Chinese, Level K, Simplified Chinese/Pinyin/CD and Workbook.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Jinan University Textbook</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The textbook is compiled by Jinan University supplemented with "Pinyin" published by Beijing Chinese Language and Culture school</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 1st Grade (中文班 1年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The First Grade is designed to assist students in beginning a systematic, second language acquisition process. The first eight to ten weeks of school will be focused on Pinyin study, learning initials, finals, tones, rules of syllables pronunciation and the combination. After Pinyin study, students gradually develop the capability to read Chinese characters with the help of Pinyin. Then by learning characters, sentences, short passages and songs in the textbook, students will be able to enhance their knowledge of basic strokes and order of strokes in a character, master common radicals, single characters (those with a single body) and basic characters that have strong word constructing ability. In the meantime, communication skills will also be developed with each real-life oral theme and cultural thread as well as through an effective teaching approach which is student-centered and interactive to promote students' interest in learning. The textbook is "Chinese" Book One (including two workbooks) supplemented with "Pinyin" and workbook.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 2nd Grade (中文班 2年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The design of the Second Grade teaching focuses on reviewing and consolidating Pinyin learned from the first grade, and expanding vocabulary through making phrases and sentences as well as language applications in actual life. Knowledge of characters, structures, order of strokes, and radicals is further developed. During the instructions, the teacher tries to strengthen students' competency in listening, speaking, and reading by means of images, gestures, songs, games, routine classroom language and a variety of other language activities. Students will also have opportunities to engage in daily dialogues, learn to understand the Chinese culture and customs, language applications, ancient poetry, tongue twisters and nursery rhymes. The textbook is "Chinese" Level Two (including two workbooks).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 3rd Grade (中文班 3年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The teaching objectives for the Third Grade continue to reinforce the basic rules and concept of Chinese language arts. By learning relevant children poems, short articles, science, stories and biographies of people in history, students are able to expand their vocabulary and its proper uses, understand and use more complex sentence structures. Chinese cultures and background will also be integrated into the teaching based on students' understanding of the chapter contents. Exercises on words of similar shapes, multi-sound words and homophones are emphasized throughout the Third Grade instruction. Depending on the content of the lesson, the teacher will introduce and allow students to practice and improve uses of some common measure words. A variety of activities will be included to strengthen students' ability to make phrases, organize sentences and improve oral presentations. The textbook is "Chinese" Book Three (including two workbooks).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 4th Grade (中文班 4年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Fourth Grade curriculum is designed to reinforce the solid basis built up in the 3rd grade learning. The objective is to master grade level words and phrases, strengthen and develop students' ability to use dictionary and study Chinese Pinyin input on computers. Reading comprehension is stressed and further developed. Besides the objectives set by the curriculum, extra reading materials are introduced in order for students to increase vocabulary, enhance word study and write longer and more complex sentences. The textbook is "Chinese" Book Four (including two workbooks).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 5th Grade (中文班 5年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The instruction of the Fifth Grade is basically maintaining the linguistic competence gained from Book Four as well as focusing on mastery of new words and expressions in Book Five. Students are assisted to further consolidate the four language skills of listening, speaking, reading and writing, with special focus on students self-teaching ability. Fifth grade students should be proficient in the 180 new words in the book --- correctly pronounce the words, recognize the shapes, and understand their meanings. They should also be able to distinguish words of similar shapes, homonyms, polyphonies, synonyms and antonyms learned before. Their competence in using measure words is emphasized too. Alphabetic-based and radical-based Dictionary look-up skills are reviewed so that students can improve their ability to interpret new words and phrases accurately and use them correctly. Enrichment activities include interesting supplementary reading materials and regularly held story-telling meetings which serve to increase students' ability to read, retell the stories and express themselves clearly and accurately. Their competence in observation and verbal expression is also strengthened by means of narrative writing according to the pictures. The textbook is "Chinese" Book Five (including two workbooks).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 6th Grade (中文班 6年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The basic instructional goal for Sixth Grade is to enhance the language skills that have been acquired from Book Five and to emphasize mastery of new words and word groups in Book Six. The ability to draw inferences from one instance will be developed in the context of instruction through analysis of radical components and the original meaning of words. Commonly used compound sentence structures, grammar points and rhetorical methods will be highlighted so that students achieve proficiency level through intensive study. Oral interpretation will be encouraged in order to build a solid foundation for future translation of written language. The lessons also include composition guidance, class publications, supplementary reading materials and introduction of Chinese history and traditional culture. We encourage more extensive reading during this year in order to enhance reading comprehension capacity. Supplementary homework will be assigned to allow more practice on how to use the Chinese language functionally in real life. A variety of teaching approaches will be employed to stimulate and increase interest and enthusiasm in learning; examples include vocabulary games, public speech contest, class discussion and debate. The textbook is "Chinese" Book Six (including two workbooks). Extensive reading and corresponding comprehensive practice compiled by CACC Chinese teachers will also be assigned.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 7th Grade (中文班 7年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The teaching objectives for the Seventh Grade are to master the new words and expressions in Book Seven on the basis of Book Six. Special emphasis will be placed on extensive reading to increase vocabulary. Composition skills will be reinforced during this period by writing short narratives. Inductive learning techniques, such as "character, event", will be employed more often. More extensive reading will be adopted in order to enhance reading comprehension capacity. Students will begin to write narrative essays. Preliminary translation techniques (from English to Chinese or vice versa) will be introduced. The textbook is "Chinese" Book Seven (including two workbooks). Extensive reading and corresponding comprehensive practice compiled by CACC Chinese teachers will also be assigned.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese 8th Grade (中文班 8年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The teaching objectives continue to focus on mastery of new words and expressions in Book Eight based on the knowledge acquired from Book Seven. Large amount of readings are supplemented to enhance competence in writing and to expand vocabulary. The textbook adopted is "Chinese" Book Eight (including two workbooks) compiled by Jinan University for oversea Chinese and Chinese learners.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Designed for students without any Chinese learning background or non-Mandarin speakers. The learning objectives are focused on communicative ability in commonly encountered language contexts and will center on themes that are relevant to daily life and culture.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language 1 (少儿汉语班 1级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Designed for students without any Chinese learning background or non-Mandarin speakers. The learning objectives are focused on communicative ability in commonly encountered language contexts and will center on themes that are relevant to daily life and culture. The learning objectives are focused on communicative ability in commonly encountered language contexts, such as greeting, introduction of one's name, nationality, family and community as well as school, sports and their favorites in life. In addition, the teacher will introduce the basics of Chinese language; examples are strokes, stroke order, and radicals. Chinese culture and cross cultural comparisons run throughout the entire year as the occasion arises. Pinyin is an integral part of the instruction to enable learners to use it as a tool to master Chinese pronunciation and tones. After the first introductory year, the learners will be able to read and write about 100 characters, use the basic sentence structures and engage in simple conversations in Chinese. The textbook used is My First Chinese Words (A set of 36 books plus CD, Simplified Chinese). The school will provide Hanyu Pinyin Textbook and Workbook by Jinan University to students as home learning aid to assist learners to supplement their classroom experience. Please note that the textbook and CD or DVD is not included in the tuition. The book fee plus DVD or CD ranges from $60 to $90 (please check and confirm the current price). Parents can buy it online at https://www.BetterChinese.com (online supplemental subscription can be purchased separately, this is optional. Free trial: https://trial.betterchinese.com/indexV.html?UUID=287ff067-c609-4219-9d49-b98379bb7854).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language 2 (少儿汉语班 2级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class offered to students who have completed CSL-1 and to any student who has some Chinese language listening/speaking background. Lessons will continue to build upon the language competence gained from CSL-1 and will center on themes that are relevant to daily life and culture. Basic knowledge of the Chinese language will be further expanded at this level as more characters and complex sentence structures are introduced. These include strokes, stroke order, radicals, Pinyin and so on. The basic communication skills of listening and speaking will be equally emphasized during instruction, with many opportunities for practice. Chinese culture will be integrated in the class throughout the year. The instructional materials include: Textbook "My First Chinese Words (A set of 36 books plus CD, Simplified Chinese) Workbook "My First Chinese Words" (Simplified Chinese). Please note that the cost of the textbook and CD or DVD is not included in the tuition. The book fees plus DVD or CD range from $60 to $90. (please check and confirm the current price). Parents can buy it online at https://www.BetterChinese.com (online supplemental subscription can be purchased separately, this is optional. Free trial: https://trial.betterchinese.com/indexV.html?UUID=287ff067-c609-4219-9d49-b98379bb7854).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language 3 (少儿汉语班 3级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is offered to students who have completed class CSL-2 and to any student who has some Chinese language listening/speaking background. Lessons will continue to build upon the language competence gained from CSL-2 and center around themes that are relevant to daily life and culture. There will be many opportunities to practice the basic communication skills of listening and speaking. Reading and writing skills will be emphasized throughout the year. The textbook used is My First Chinese Reader Vol. 1 (Textbook and Workbook, Simplified Chinese). Please note that the cost of the textbook and CD or DVD is not included in the tuition. The book fees plus DVD or CD range from $60 to $90. (please check and confirm the current price). Parents can buy it online at https://www.BetterChinese.com (online supplemental subscription can be purchased separately, this is optional. Free trial: https://trial.betterchinese.com/indexV.html?UUID=287ff067-c609-4219-9d49-b98379bb7854).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language 4 (少儿汉语班 4级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is offered to students who have completed 'CSL III' and to any student who has strong Chinese language listening/speaking background. Lessons will continue to build upon the language competence gained from Level III and will focus on themes that are relevant to daily life and culture. Basic knowledge of the Chinese language will be further expanded at this level as more characters and complex sentence structures are introduced. These basic knowledge and skills include knowing and practicing character strokes, stroke orders, radicals, Pinyin and so on. The basic communication skills of listening and speaking will be equally emphasized during instruction, with many opportunities for practice. Chinese culture will be integrated in the class throughout the year. The textbook for this course is "My First Chinese Reader Vol. 2 (Textbook and Workbook, Simplified Chinese)". Please note that the cost of the textbook and CD or DVD is not included in the tuition. The book fee plus DVD or CD range from $60 to $90. For current prices of the textbook, workbook, and CD or DVD, please check and confirm with BetterChinese. Parents can buy all study materials online at https://www.BetterChinese.com (online supplemental subscription can be purchased separately, this is optional. Free trial: https://trial.betterchinese.com/indexV.html?UUID=287ff067-c609-4219-9d49-b98379bb7854).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language 5 (少儿汉语班 5级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is offered to students who have completed CSL-4 and to any student who has strong Chinese language listening/speaking background. Lessons will continue to build upon the language competence gained from CSL-4 and will focus on themes that are relevant to daily life and culture. Basic knowledge of the Chinese language will be further expanded at this level as more characters and complex sentence structures are introduced. The basic communication skills of listening and speaking will be equally emphasized during instruction, with many opportunities for practice. Chinese culture will be integrated in the class throughout the year. The textbook used is My First Chinese Reader Vol. 3 (Textbook and Workbook, Simplified Chinese). Please note that the cost of the textbook and CD or DVD is not included in the tuition. The book fee plus DVD or CD range from $60 to $90. For current prices of the textbook, workbook, and CD or DVD, please check and confirm with BetterChinese. Parents can buy all study materials online at https://www.BetterChinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese as a Second Language 7 (少儿汉语班 7级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is offered to students who have completed CSL-6 and to any student who has been recommended through an assessment given by the school. Lessons will continue to build upon the language competence gained from CSL-6 and will focus on themes that are relevant to daily life and culture. Basic knowledge of the Chinese language will be further expanded at this level as more characters and complex sentence structures are introduced. The basic communication skills of listening and speaking will be equally emphasized during instruction, with many opportunities for practice. Chinese culture will be integrated in the class throughout the year. The textbook used is Discovering Chinese Pro New Edition Simplified Chinese Volume 3 (Textbook and Workbook). Please note that the cost of the textbook, workbook, and CD or DVD is not included in the tuition. The book fee plus DVD or CD range from $60 to $90. For current prices of the textbook, workbook, and CD or DVD, please check and confirm with BetterChinese. Parents can buy all study materials online at https://www.BetterChinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Ma Li Ping Chinese Textbook</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Ma Li Ping Chinese Text Book and Learning Materials are designed for children born overseas to learn about authentic Chinese culture. Their most important features are:</answer_text>
            <list_item>
                <category>the refined content and presentation</category>
            </list_item>
            <list_item>
                <category>the direct learning approach with words and literacy</category>
            </list_item>
            <list_item>
                <category>the teaching of Pinyin in later stages</category>
            </list_item>
            <list_item>
                <category>recognizing words at first and writing them at second</category>
            </list_item>
            <list_item>
                <category>focusing more on words-recognizing than on words-writing</category>
            </list_item>
            <list_item>
                <category>reading at first and writing at second</category>
            </list_item>
            <list_item>
                <category>allow Chinese learning in a natural way</category>
            </list_item>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 1 (斯坦福中文马立平教材1年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The teaching goal for the first year is to develop the ability of students to directly identify Chinese characters without Pinyin, through a selection of verse teaching. A standardized and specified teaching progresses through vocabulary, words and sentences reading, verse learning, stroke-writing exercises, character structures, classroom copybooks to learn how to write, etc. - a variety of language learning activities. The textbook has innovated ideographic radicals and phonetic radical concept, clearly summarizes and classifies Chinese characters and make them easy to remember, so students may quickly grasp the strokes, the pen shape, the stroke order and the radicals of the vocabulary. Fun verse text and reading jokes are incorporated into the textbook to help students easily and naturally recognize Chinese characters and culture. The weekly homework is novel in form, multimedia, that integrates listening, speaking, reading, writing and all-round practice and exercise games to make learning easy and to make Chinese learning fun. During the school year, the student will cumulatively learn 302 commonly used Chinese characters. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese First Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 2 (斯坦福中文马立平教材2年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The characteristics of Ma Li Ping Chinese Text Book and Learning Materials for the second grade are: 1. emphasizing vocabulary recognizing and reading; 2. words-recognizing at first and writing at second; 3. focusing more on words-recognizing than on words-writing; 4. start from reading and putting writing at later time; 5. And allow Chinese learning in a natural way. The content of Ma Li Ping Chinese Text Book and Learning Materials for the second grade has a great amount of vocabulary and literacy and focuses on reading ability training. Both texts and reading materials are taught in detail; each lesson is equipped with short interesting stories of diverse subjects, quickly and effectively pushing students to master a lot of vocabulary to improve their Chinese reading ability. Through concise and clear grammar summary as well as grammar patterns practice, students will improve their oral expression and words and sentences usage. Also based on the practice of easy-to-remember ideographic radicals and phonetic radical concept and based on the exercises of polyphone, homophone, and similar-form words, we will learn new material while reviewing the learned vocabulary, and reach a broader extent of knowledge from what has been learned previously. While teaching from the textbook, the teacher will introduce and present the related Chinese culture and background. The form of weekly homework is pretty novel, as student will use both textbook and multimedia simultaneously, integrating listening, speaking, reading, writing and all-round practice and exercise games to transfer any difficulty into ease and to make Chinese learning joyful. During the school year student will cumulatively learn 683 commonly-used Chinese characters. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese Second Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 3 (斯坦福中文马立平教材3年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The content of Ma Li Ping Chinese Text Book and Learning Materials for the 3rd grade has a great amount of vocabulary and literacy and focuses on reading ability training. Both texts and reading materials are taught in detail; each lesson is equipped with short interesting stories of diverse subjects, quickly and effectively pushing students to master a lot of vocabulary to improve their Chinese reading ability. Through concise and clear grammar summary as well as grammar patterns practice, students will improve their oral expression and words and sentences usage. Also based on the practice of easy-to-remember ideographic radicals and phonetic radical concept and based on the exercises of polyphone, homophone, and similar-form words, we will learn new material while reviewing the learned vocabulary, and reach a broader extent of knowledge from what has been learned previously. While teaching from the textbook, the teacher will introduce and present the related Chinese culture and background. The form of weekly homework is pretty novel, as student will use both textbook and multimedia simultaneously, integrating listening, speaking, reading, writing and all-round practice and exercise games to transfer any difficulty into ease and to make Chinese learning joyful. During the school year student will cumulatively learn 1047 commonly-used Chinese characters. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese 3rd Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 4 (斯坦福中文马立平教材4年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The fourth year of the Ma Li Ping Chinese Text Book is a continuation from the first three years of direct character recognition (with the focus of character recognition in years 1 and 2 and pinyin added in year 3) and an important advancement stage in learning the Chinese language. In this course, both the instructional materials and the instructional strategies focus on meeting the needs of heritage learners by adopting texts and additional reading materials that supplement each other in many ways, which is reflected by having every lesson consist of multiple fun and famous stories that reflect the Chinese history and culture helping to reach the goals of learning the language and culture at the same time. The fourth year will continue to focus on character recognition and reading instruction to help students enlarge their vocabulary for a solid foundation to write Chinese compositions at the next step. Upon completion of four years of learning, students will have learned/ accumulated a total number of 1384 Chinese characters, in which literacy and grammar instruction is an important part. Furthermore, in order to follow the integral instructional principles to use localized instructional materials, to recognize more than writing, to read before writing, homework assignments will continue to follow the lively and fun format, in which students will have the multimedia to help them read aloud each text, see writing demos, play games with new words and vocabulary so that they will enjoy working on the homework in a free, open and fun atmosphere to achieve the goals of improving abilities in listening, speaking , reading and writing Chinese. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese 4th Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee $60 -65 ( please check and confirm the current price) is not included in the tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 5 (斯坦福中文马立平教材5年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Fifth Year of the Ma Li Ping Chinese Textbook presents an important transitional stage from the first four years of direct character recognition and reading with Pinyin introduced in the third year. During this transitional period, the fifth year course offers students an opportunity to develop their basic reading skills to a higher level of application. On the basis of Pinyin knowledge learned in the third year, students will review and distinguish characteristics of the Pinyin system with an emphasis on computer inputting for Chinese characters using the Pinyin system; meanwhile they will learn how to use a Chinese dictionary by using Pinyin, radical/component, and stroke indexing, in order to develop skills needed in using a convenient tool to study Chinese at a higher level. The structure of the textbook demonstrates the goals for using the language at a higher level and in a wider range, e.g. Unit Four of the textbook includes an adapted version of Chapter 20 in the classical Chinese novel "The Journey to the West". This not only provides an opportunity for students to be exposed to a masterpiece of the classical Chinese literature in an interesting form of the adapted version to learn about the Chinese literature and history, they also learn the brilliant language and culture as well as some dramatic describing techniques, which will help to lay a solid foundation in creative writing skills needed as a transition to the Sixth Grade when creative writing will be the major focus. Upon completion of the fifth year of learning of this series, students should have set up a basic foundation in listening, speaking, reading and writing Chinese. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese the 5th Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 6 (斯坦福中文马立平教材6年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>With the basis established during previous years of study in basic Chinese language vocabulary building (grades 1-4) and reading skills building (grade 5) through reading a variety of literary selections including an adapted version of the classical Chinese novel "The Journey to the West", the student should have experienced reading descriptive works. The focus in the 6th grade will be to develop student's writing skills, especially in descriptive writing. Texts in Unit One integrates classical Chinese folktales and modern Children's stories in forms of cross-talk and story-telling to help students understand how to effectively describe things and characters in a story. Those folktales and stories will also provide students opportunities to learn about the Chinese culture. Texts in Units Two and Three will present a series of lessons on writing skills in the form of 'Teacher Ma Talks about Writing' in eight different lessons. Each lesson will include a writing sample that correlates the specific writing skills addressed. Those lessons with writing samples are designed to systematically address writing skills. It is our hope that studies in the 6th grade will not only improve each student's writing skills, but will also greatly improve their skills in using the language in general so that they can better use the Chinese language in everyday life. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese the 6th Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 7 (斯坦福中文马立平教材7年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>With the basic writing knowledge and skills obtained in the 6th grade study, the focus in the 7th grade will continue to be writing skills and intensive reading of selected literary works. Besides working on each writing component such as selecting appropriate topics, themes, beginning, middle and end, Units I and II will continue to present a series of lessons on writing skills in the form of 'Teacher Ma Talks about Writing' in eight different lessons. In these series of lessons, students will have a further study in how to describe the personality and specific features of a character in a writing through applying techniques such as creating a plot, establishing a theme, using imagination, using dialogues, and describing facial expressions and physical actions as well as appearance, etc. Unit III is a unit about visiting China. Through reading simplified descriptions illustrated with beautiful pictures, students will get a direct feeling of the charm of beautiful natural sceneries and places of historical figures and cultural heritage in China. This will provide students with opportunities to learn about Chinese history and background knowledge of the Chinese culture. In a word, the main theme of the textbook for the 7th grade will provide students with opportunities to progress to a solid higher level in writing skills in Chinese. They will also get to know the concept of "the theory that man is an integral part of nature". The 7th grade of this textbook series is a rather valuable learning experience for students.The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese the 7th Grade" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer.Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Stanford Chinese 8 (斯坦福中文马立平教材8年级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>For our newly established 8th grade Stanford Chinese course, we feel fortunate to have the newly (2019) revised version of this textbook series. This new version of the textbook for the 8th grade was re-organized by the author through combining carefully selected contents/lessons from the previous version of the textbook for 8th and 9th grades. Those changes were made to meet the US school system so that students will be able to complete studying the whole series by the time they enter the 9th grade, thus the current version of the textbook is the best from the best and enables our students to spend one year to complete studying the contents that were previously planned for two years. This new textbook for the 8th graders entitled "The Window of Chinese Cultures" (Volumes 22 to 24), provides the stage of learning of literature and cultures, which is divided into three units: Inspirations, Poems &amp; Paintings, and Historical Figures. At this stage of learning, students will have opportunities to learn about Chinese literature and learn how to appreciate selected masterpieces of the Chinese literature, which will enable them to learn about the essence of traditional Chinese culture and thoughts. There will be various genres in Chinese literature (Confucius Analects, ancient poems, folk songs, prose, as well as in form of folk tales) in introducing the Chinese culture. Study of this textbook will enable students to learn about the sources of the Chinese literature and thoughts through the study of Chinese history, geography, cultural knowledge, as well as selected literati/authors and famous historical figures. Supplementary readings following each lesson will provide students with a wider and deeper understanding of what was learned in the text during the week. Many of the supplementary reading materials are in the form of prose rich in life wisdoms and philosophy, which is both entertaining and informative for learning. The textbook is rich in content and informative with a large vocabulary and a wide range of knowledge for reading. Through a careful study of this set of the textbook, students will be given an opportunity to better reach the goals of learning the Chinese language through strengthening and raising the overall ability in listening, speaking, reading, and writing the language. The textbooks are "Ma Li Ping Chinese the 8th Grade (The Window of Chinese Cultures)" and two workbooks A and B with multimedia homework and color flashcards for each lesson, as well as a practice workbook for continued review in the summer. Textbook material fee ($60 -65, please check the price) excluded from tuition fee. Families are responsible for acquiring the necessary textbooks/workbooks on their own. You may also buy the books yourself at www.heritagechinese.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Prep Course for High School Chinese III (高中学分班预备班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Pre-requisite: With home language background in Chinese and some Chinese language study but not yet ready to enter Chinese III This Prep Course for High School Chinese credit course is designed to prepare students with some Chinese language background who need the preparation to enter the High School Chinese Program. The current High School Chinese Program starts from Level III, for which this course is to prepare those students who are NOT YET ready to go to Level III to get the language skills and proficiency needed to enter Level III of the High School Chinese Program. This course lasts for three hours each week and does not offer credits due to its nature as a prep course. Students who successfully completed this prep course with a grade of C or higher will be recommended to Chinese III for the next school year without taking the placement test. The High School Chinese Program is designed for high school students who are interested in Chinese and want to meet UC and CSU 'e' (World Language) requirements. Currently, we have three levels: Chinese III, IV and AP. These classes have been accredited by The Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC) and are approved to be placed on Pleasanton Unified School District transcript in order to meet UC/CSU "e" requirements. By taking these classes, a student can earn his/her high school credit and meet the (e) requirements of the UC/CSU category of language other than English. The textbook for these courses is 'Integrated Chinese', which has been used as the teaching material by UC Berkeley and other colleges for more than 10 years. The program focuses on Chinese language learning as a system. The textbook uses real-life examples as the main teaching material, enabling students to position themselves in a real Chinese language environment. In the textbook, each lesson starts with a real-life conversation, plus extensive practice through listening, speaking, reading, and writing. The materials are selected in order for a good understanding of Chinese history and culture to provide a better fit for high school learners. The program is created in accordance with California high school course requirements, including classroom hours, projects, and labs. There are two semesters per school year. A letter grade system (A, B, C,) will be used. Students who are already in high school or entering high school in Fall 2021 are welcome to enroll in our High School classes through a placement test for proper placements into the Program. In order to properly place each student, there will be a placement test for new students who want to take High School III, IV, or AP level. As it is a placement test to determine a student's actual level, students will not need to prepare for this test. Please note that the cost of the textbook and workbook is not included in the tuition. You may purchase the books yourself at www.amazon.com or www.cheng-tsui.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Chinese AP Prep (中文 AP 备考)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>"Chinese CAP" is designed to help high school students take the AP Chinese test and learn how to appreciate classical and modern Chinese language and culture. The course is prepared according to the AP Chinese test guidelines established by the College Board. Through integrated teaching of the language and culture, the class emphasizes listening, speaking, reading, and writing skills. AP Chinese tests are available for students to practice the skills that they have learned. The materials for this course are excerpted from the textbook "Step Up to AP" and tailored to meet the requirements for the AP Chinese test. To better prepare students for the AP Chinese exam, this course intentionally adds readings about traditional Chinese culture, broadens the reading of modern Chinese literature and current issues, and improves students' written and oral presentation skills. All lessons are designed to follow 5C's (Communication, Culture, Connections, Comparisons, and Communities) and the three modes of communication (Interpersonal, Interpretive, and Presentational) to meet the requirements by the College Board. The entire class will be taught in Chinese. After completing this course, students should acquire the skills and the knowledge necessary to do well on the AP Chinese exam. This course is intended for students who have completed our High School Chinese III, or equivalent. Please note that the cost of the textbook and workbook is not included in the tuition. You may purchase the books yourself at www.amazon.com or ngl.cengage.com. Alternatively, you can add textbooks during class registration, while supplies last and on a first-come, first-served basis. Please note this is a two-hour course without high school credit.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>High School Chinese III (高中学分班 III)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Pre-requisite: Passing grade in "Prep course for High School Chinese III (高中学分班预备班)" or Placement test showing adequate preparations at equivalent language proficiency level. The High School Program is designed for high school students who are interested in Chinese and want to meet UC and CSU 'e' (World Language) requirements. Currently we have three levels: Chinese III, IV and AP. These classes have been accredited by The Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC) and are approved to be placed on Pleasanton Unified School District transcript in order to meet UC/CSU "e" requirements. By taking these classes, a student can earn his/her high school credit and meet the (e) requirements of the UC/CSU category of language other than English. The textbook for these courses is 'Integrated Chinese', which has been used as the teaching materials by UC Berkeley and other colleges for more than 10 years. The program focuses on Chinese language learning as a system. The textbook uses real-life examples as the main teaching material, enabling students to position themselves into a real Chinese language environment. In the textbook, each lesson starts with a real life conversation, plus extensive practice through listening, speaking, reading and writing. The materials are selected in order for a good understanding of Chinese history and culture to provide a better fit for high school learners. The program is created in accordance with California high school course requirements, including classroom hours, projects and labs hours. There are two semesters per school year. A letter grade system (A, B, C,...) will be used. Students who are already in high school or entering high school in the fall semester are welcome to enroll in our High School Chinese classes. Pre-requisite: successful completion of Prep course for High School Chinese III with a grade C or above, or equivalent (with placement test). For students who are entering our high school program as a new student will be asked to take a placement test, which is usually given in the spring semester each year. Please note that the cost of the textbook and workbook is not included in the tuition. You may purchase the books yourself at www.amazon.com or www.cheng-tsui.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>High School Chinese IV (高中学分班 IV)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Pre-requisite: Passing grade in "Prep course for High School Chinese III (高中学分班预备班)" or Placement test showing adequate preparations at equivalent language proficiency level. The High School Program is designed for high school students who are interested in Chinese and want to meet UC and CSU 'e' (World Language) requirement. Currently we have three levels: Chinese III, IV and AP. These classes have been accredited by The Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC) and are approved to be placed on Pleasanton Unified School District transcript in order to meet UC/CSU "e" requirements. By taking these classes, a student can earn his/her high school credit and meet the (e) requirements of the UC/CSU category of language other than English. The textbook for these courses is 'Integrated Chinese', which has been used as the teaching materials by UC Berkeley and other colleges for more than 10 years. The program focuses on Chinese language learning as a system. The textbook uses real-life examples as the main teaching material, enabling students to position themselves into a real Chinese language environment. In the textbook, each lesson starts with a real life conversation, plus extensive practice through listening, speaking, reading and writing. The materials are selected in order for a good understanding of Chinese history and culture to provide a better fit for high school learners. The program is created in accordance with California high school course requirements, including classroom hours, projects and labs hours. There are two semesters per school year. A letter grade system (A, B, C,...) will be used. Students who are already in high school or entering high school in the fall semester are welcome to enroll in our High School Chinese classes; Students who have successfully completed Chinese III will be recommendation for Chinese IV. Pre-requisite: successful completion of Chinese III with a grade C or above, or equivalent (with a placement test). For students who are entering our high school program as a new student will be asked to take a placement test, which is usually given in the spring semester each year. Please note that the cost of the textbook and workbook is not included in the tuition. You may purchase the books yourself at www.amazon.com or www.cheng-tsui.com.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>High School Chinese AP (高中学分班 AP)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Pre-requisite: Passing grade in High School Chinese IV or Placement test showing adequate preparations at equivalent language proficiency level. The High School Program is designed for high school students who are interested in Chinese and want to meet UC and CSU 'e' (World Language) requirement. Currently we have three levels: Chinese III, IV and AP. These classes have been accredited by The Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC) and are approved to be placed on Pleasanton Unified School District transcript in order to meet UC/CSU "e" requirements. By taking these classes, a student can earn his/her high school credit and meet the (e) requirements of the UC/CSU category of language other than English. The course is prepared according to the AP Chinese test guidelines established by the College Board. Through integrated teaching of the language and culture, the class emphasizes listening, speaking, reading, and writing skills. To better prepare students for the AP Chinese Language and Culture exam, we have chosen the textbook for these courses 'Step Up to AP: Chinese Language, Culture, and Society'. This course intentionally adds readings about traditional Chinese culture, broadens the reading of modern Chinese literature and current issues, and improves students' written and oral presentation skills. All lessons are designed to follow 5C's (Communication, Culture, Connections, Comparisons, and Communities) and the three modes of communication (Interpersonal, Interpretive, and Presentational) in order to meet the requirements by the College Board. The entire class will be taught in Chinese. After completing this course, students should acquire the skills and the knowledge necessary to do well on the AP Chinese Language and Culture Exam. The program is created in accordance with California high school course requirements, including classroom hours, projects and labs hours. There are two semesters per school year. A letter grade system (A, B, C,...) will be used. Students who are already in high school or entering high school in fall semester are welcome to enroll in our High School classes. In order to properly place each student, there will be a placement test for new students who want to take High School III, IV or AP. Please note: Due to limited access to facilities at CACC Chinese School, we do not provide assistance in registering for the AP Chinese Language and Culture Exam in May of each year. Each student is expected to return to the high school where he or she is enrolled to seek assistance in obtaining a spot for the AP Chinese Language and Culture Exam. Please note that the cost of the textbook and workbook is not included in the tuition. You may purchase the books yourself at www.amazon.com or ngl.cengage.com. Alternatively, you can add textbooks during class registration, while supplies last and on a first-come, first-served basis.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>