<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Tennis Beginner (网球初级班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Course Objectives: This course is designed for beginners or students with no prior experience. It aims to help students learn basic tennis techniques and rules while developing good exercise habits and teamwork skills. Course Content: Fundamental techniques: serving, receiving, forehand, and basic footwork and court positioning. Simple practice drills and mini-games. The classes will be taught in English.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Tennis Intermediate (网球中级班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Course Objectives: This course is designed to improve students' tennis skills, enhance their competitive play abilities, and deepen their understanding and application of tennis rules and strategies. Students will be broken into groups based on age and skill level. Classes will focus on developing proper technique and rally skills. The classes will be taught in English.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Tennis Advanced (网球提高班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is for advanced players only, ages 11 and up. This class will focus on advanced technique and match play skills. This class is ideal for students looking to improve for high school, middle school or USTA tournaments. The program is not designed for high level players or intense training. The classes will be taught in English.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Children Badminton Beginner (少儿羽毛球初级班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is perfect for kids who are brand new to badminton or have less than one year of experience. Young players will be introduced to the fundamentals of the game in a fun and supportive environment. They will learn proper grip and swing techniques to build a strong foundation, along with essential footwork to move efficiently on the court. Students will also be introduced to the rules and basic strategies of both singles and doubles play. Whether they're picking up a racket for the first time or just getting started, this class will help them develop confidence and skills to enjoy the game of badminton. According to the Chinese School's full academic year schedule, there are a total of 31 sessions planned course. However, on the last Sundays of the school year, the large gym at Amador High School may be reserved for other events, which could result in the cancellation of two badminton sessions. We will notify you in advance if this occurs. Tuition fees have already been adjusted to account for this possibility.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Children Badminton Intermediate (少儿羽毛球中级班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Designed for kids who have taken 1-2 group lessons at CACC, this intermediate class helps players build on their foundational skills and advance their game. Students should already be familiar with basic techniques and be able to perform a variety of shots, including serve, clear, lift, drop, drive, and smash. In this class, players will continue refining their technique, improving consistency, and developing better shot control. They'll also enhance their tactical understanding and court awareness through structured drills and match play in both singles and doubles formats. This class is ideal for young athletes ready to take their badminton skills to the next level. Coaches will group students based on skill level and provide personalized instruction to ensure each player receives the guidance they need to reach their full potential. According to the Chinese School's full academic year schedule, there are a total of 31 sessions planned course. However, on the last Sundays of the school year, the large gym at Amador High School may be reserved for other events, which could result in the cancellation of two badminton sessions. We will notify you in advance if this occurs. Tuition fees have already been adjusted to account for this possibility.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Children's Drawing</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Children's Drawing Class Teaching Objectives. Inspire artistic interest and creativity. Encourage children to enjoy the process of making art while exploring their imagination. Build foundational drawing skills. Develop control, technique, and confidence in using various drawing tools and materials. Understand key elements of art. Introduce essential concepts such as color mixing, form, space, texture, and composition. Enhance observation and aesthetic awareness. Strengthen students' ability to observe details, appreciate visual beauty, and express themselves through hands-on projects.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Drawing I (绘画 I 级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Beginner Class (Ages 5-8) Learning and Growth Patterns at This Age: Developing fine motor skills: Children at this age are still gaining control of their hand movements, making simple drawing and craft activities ideal. Enjoy spontaneous expression: They love doodling and expressing themselves freely. Drawn to bright colors and playful themes: Bold colors, animals, and fairy tale elements easily capture their interest. Instructional Goals: Color recognition and coordination: Learning to identify and combine colors. Basic shapes and drawing: Exploring simple forms and how to use them in pictures. Introduction to crafting: Hands-on activities like paper cutting and pasting to develop creativity and motor skills. Lesson Examples: Little Animals Basic Shapes Teach children how to draw simple animals like cats, dogs, and rabbits. Complete the scene with a background made from cut-out paper grass. Magic Tree Creative Expression Use handprints to form the trunk and branches of a tree. Add colorful paper leaves and fruits to bring it to life in a fun and imaginative way.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Drawing II (绘画 II 级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Intermediate Class (Ages 8-10) Learning and Growth Patterns at This Age: Improved hand-eye coordination: Students begin creating art with more control and purpose. Attention to detail: They start to observe more closely and express ideas with intention. Interest in composition: A growing curiosity about how elements like shape, space, and color work together in a piece. Instructional Goals: Foundations of sketching and drawing: Exploring outlines, shading, and pencil techniques. Understanding composition and proportion: Learning how to balance elements within a drawing and use color harmoniously. Art appreciation: Introduction to famous artists such as Van Gogh and Monet to connect technique with historical context. Lesson Examples: Still Life World Sketching Basics (Outlines &amp; Light/Shadow) Students learn to draw everyday objects like an apple and a glass, practicing contour lines and shading to capture light and depth. Dream House Introduction to Perspective Children design their own dream building while learning one-point perspective, adding depth and dimension to their drawings. The Story of Sunflowers Impressionism Inspired by Van Gogh, students create vibrant sunflower artworks using oil pastels, exploring brushstroke style and expressive color. Color Conversations Color Theory - Complementary &amp; Warm/Cool Colors Using contrasting color pairs, students make abstract artworks that express mood and emotion through color choices.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Drawing III (绘画 III 级)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Advanced Art Class (Ages 11-13) Learning and Growth Patterns at This Age: More mature thinking: Students begin to form personal opinions and develop an ability to evaluate aesthetics. Ready for theory and technique: They can absorb more structured lessons in art fundamentals and artistic methods. Expressive and symbolic work: Art becomes a deeper form of self-expression, often centered around emotion and personal themes. Instructional Goals: Advanced sketching and color practice: Refining techniques in shading, proportion, and color application. Creative thinking and concept development: Encouraging students to plan and create artwork with intentional themes. Exploration of painting techniques: Introducing watercolor and gouache, focusing on blending, texture, and layering. Lesson Examples: Character Sketch Portrait Proportion and Observation Students draw self-portraits using mirrors, learning facial proportions and practicing accuracy and shading in their sketches. Emotional Expression	Abstract Symbolism Using color, shape, and composition, students create abstract artworks that express a chosen emotion such as joy, fear, or loneliness. Watercolor Techniques Blending and Reflection Students explore basic watercolor techniques—such as wet-on-wet blending and transparency—by painting natural scenes with lakes and reflections.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>