<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Who organizes and runs the school?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Chinese American Cooperation Council (CACC), a non-profit organization headquartered in Pleasanton, California, has sponsored and organized CACC Chinese School since 2003. As the governing body of CACC and its affairs, the Board of Directors oversees the management of CACC Chinese School. The school principal, along with his/her staff and volunteers, runs the daily operations of the school and is responsible for the success of all activities.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Where is the school located?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The CACC Chinese School currently rents facility space at Amador Valley High School, located at 1155 Santa Rita Road, Pleasanton, CA 94566. Office service hour is every Sunday when school is in session, 9:30am - 12:30pm</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>What programs do we offer?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Chinese American Cooperation Council (CACC) Chinese School was established to build better communities and develop future leaders who appreciate diversity, understand global challenges, are confident and inspiring, and are eager to serve local communities and the world. It has six programs and many student leadership opportunities, more than 1,900 registrations and 1,300 students, and offers almost 100 classes taught by some of the best instructors from China and America. Non-Chinese speakers are welcome and many are very successful at the school.</answer_text>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Chinese as a Second Language for Non-Chinese Speakers</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Chinese for Elementary and Middle School Students (Pre-Kindergarten, Kindergarten, First Grade to Eighth Grade)</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>High School Chinese Credit Classes, AP Chinese Class, and AP Chinese Prep Class (for AP test preparation)</category>
                    <category_example>High School Chinese Program (Levels I, II, III, IV and AP Chinese) -- meet UC/CSU 'e'(world language) requirement</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Competitive Math</category>
                    <category_example>Math Olympiad</category_example>
                    <category_example>Competitive Math</category_example>
                    <category_example>AMC 10 and Pre-AIME</category_example>
                    <category_example>Singapore Math</category_example>
                    <category_example>Math Competitions (Math Olympiad, Mathleague, AMC8/AMC10, Math Kangaroo, etc.)</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Children Enrichment Program</category>
                    <category_example>Basketball, Badminton, Kung Fu and Tennis</category_example>
                    <category_example>Chess</category_example>
                    <category_example>Arts and Drawing</category_example>
                    <category_example>Dance</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Adult and Senior Enrichment Program</category>
                    <category_example>Zumba, Chinese Dance, Aerobic Dance, U-Jam, Singing Arts, and Choir</category_example>
                    <category_example>Basketball, Volleyball, Badminton, Photography, Drawing</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Activities for Leadership Development and Mentoring</category>
                    <category_example>Seminars for Extracurricular, College Planning, Real Estate and more</category_example>
                    <category_example>Extracurricular, Volunteer, and Leadership Opportunities</category_example>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>When are classes in session?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The school is open on Sundays from 9:00am to 1:00pm from late August to late May at Amador Valley High School in Pleasanton. The school is closed in summer. Please see school calendar</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Would CACC Chinese School terminate a student's enrollment during the school year?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>All the students at CACC Chinese School are required to follow the student guidelines. The school will work hard with students, parents, teachers, and staff to resolve students' problems. However, CACC Chinese School reserves the right to terminate a student's enrollment from the school at any time to maintain the safety and/or the quality of teaching and learning at the school.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>