<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Competitive Math (竞赛数学须知)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Competitive Math is a series of classes for gifted math students who seek a greater challenge in mathematics. We offer three levels of competitive math classes: Level I, II and III with increasing challenges. Students can enroll a class based on their school grade level. The teaching is based on guiding students to use the concepts taught in class to figure out the problems on their own, rather than teacher showing 'how it is done. These classes help students to improve their ability in comprehension, logic and problem solving skills in general. It helps them to prepare for math competitions and excel in math in regular classrooms. We encourage students to attend math competitions offered by many math institutions throughout the school year. Homework: 0.5 to 1 hour homework is required every week depending on class level. The classes will be taught in English. Note: The Math Kangaroo competition is held every March. Registration for the Math Kangaroo competition usually begins in October of the previous year through the official Math Kangaroo website. Students can participate starting from Grade 1 or Grade 2. Parents can select the nearest testing center for their child to take the exam.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Competitive Math I (竞赛数学 I)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Class Content: In this class, students build strong reasoning skills through a wide range of mathematical contexts, including numeracy, visualization, logic, and pattern recognition. The focus is on developing deep understanding and logical thinking, rather than strictly following Common Core curriculum materials. Helping younger students understand mathematical figures and shapes—and guiding them to translate these into mathematical expressions—provides an ideal foundation for beginners preparing to participate in future math competitions. This course serves as an excellent introduction, building both confidence and core problem-solving skills. Topics we explore include: Counting, Addition/Subtraction, Fractions, Ordering and comparing objects, Recognizing and creating patterns, Solving puzzles involving mazes and shapes, Working with Venn diagrams, and Introducing foundational ideas in pre-algebra. Our goal is to make math engaging, thought-provoking, and fun—encouraging students to think critically and creatively. Who Can Enroll: Students in grades 1-2 who are comfortable with addition and subtraction and possess strong reading comprehension skills. Competitive Goals: Primary competitions include Math Kangaroo (levels 1-3). We may also include preparation for Noetic Math (levels 1-2).</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Competitive Math II (竞赛数学 II)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>In this class, we focus on grade-level appropriate problem-solving strategies to help students build strong mathematical thinking and confidence. Through hands-on activities and thoughtful exploration, students deepen their understanding of key math concepts while developing critical thinking skills. Topics include: Geometry and spatial reasoning, Measurement of area and perimeter, Symmetry and visual patterns, Basic operations with positive and negative numbers, Averages, multiples, and divisors, Logic strategies and object classification, Foundational pre-algebra concepts. Our approach encourages curiosity, creativity, and a deeper appreciation for how math connects to the world around us. Who Can Enroll: Students in grades 3 or 4 who are comfortable with multiplication and division, including problems with remainders. Competitive Goals: Our target competitions include Math Kangaroo (grades 3-5). We may also prepare students for Noetic Math (levels 2-4) and/or Mathleague Elementary competitions.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Competitive Math III (竞赛数学 III)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Class Content: This class is designed for advanced elementary and middle school students who want to strengthen their problem-solving strategies and develop contest-taking skills. Instruction focuses on deeper mathematical thinking, step-by-step reasoning, and creative approaches to solving challenging problems. Key topics include: Geometry, Plane geometry, Points, lines, and segments, Circles, (special) triangles, quadrilaterals, and Symmetry. Numbers &amp; Algebra: Calculations with natural numbers, Greatest Common Factor (GCF) and Least Common Multiple (LCM), Word problems involving time, distance, and rates, Decimal and fraction operations, Logical multi-step problems and analytical reasoning, Algebraic thinking with easy algebraic notation. Who May Enroll: This course is best suited for students in grades 5 or 6 (or those working at an equivalent math level). Students should be comfortable working with fractions, basic percents, ratios, and rates. Competitive Goals: This class helps students prepare for a variety of math competitions, including: Math Kangaroo (Grades 5-6), Noetic Math Contest (Levels 4-6) (optional), Math Olympiads Elementary Section &amp; Middle School Section, Mathcounts</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Math Olympiads (奥数)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>CACC Chinese School Math Olympiads program includes three levels of math classes: beginner, intermediate, and advanced. The students can take the online self-assessment test to see which level of class is appropriate for them. The purpose of the classes is to stimulate students' interest and enthusiasm for problem solving. Students will be exposed to challenging problems, interesting puzzles, and associated mathematics topics. They will work on past Math Olympiads problems both individually and in groups. Throughout the class, the student will learn critical thinking skills and different problem-solving strategies. In these classes, we offer Math Olympiads competitions. Individual awards will be given out at the end of each school year. The classes will be taught in English. About the teacher: Ms. Qiping Guo graduated from Shanghai Jiao Tong University. She has been teaching competitive mathematics for over 17 years at CACC and various educational centers across the Tri-Valley area. Specializing in Math Olympiads and MATHCOUNTS, Ms. Guo brings a deep passion and enthusiasm to mathematics education. Known for her meticulous organization and thorough preparation, she consistently ensures that her classes are engaging and enriching. Ms. Guo employs customized teaching materials and methods tailored to each student's needs, aiming to instill robust problem-solving skills and an appreciation for the beauty of mathematics. Her students’ achievements include numerous perfect scores in MOEMS and AMC8, first-place wins in MATHCOUNTS Chapter competitions, positions on MATHCOUNTS State teams, and qualifications for AIME and the prestigious USAJMO/USAMO. Many of her students continue to excel long after graduating from her classes, gaining admission to highly selective colleges and becoming high achievers in their academic and professional pursuits.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Math Olympiads I (奥数 I)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is designed for 4th grade students and advanced 3rd graders. In this class, the students will learn basic problem-solving strategies, such as Guessing and Checking, Working Backwards, Drawing a Picture or Diagram, Looking for a pattern, Experimenting, Using a Table, Making an Organized List, etc. This class's curriculum corresponds to the material of the National Math Olympiads Division E Contests. Who may enroll: Students at regular school grade level of 3-4. A pre-test is not required. Note: $20 material fee will be collected with tuition at registration.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Math Olympiads II (奥数 II)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is designed for 5th-6th grade students and advanced 4th graders. In this class, the students will learn more advanced topics and problem solving strategies, such as Pattern and Sum, Factor and Prime, Divisibility Theorems, Geometry and Measurement, Cryptarithms, Use Logical Reasoning, Working with Exponents, Writing an Equation, etc. This class's curriculum corresponds to the material of the National Math Olympiad Division E Contests. Who may enroll: Students at regular school grade levels of 4, 5, and 6, and who were able to score 2 or higher on the 30-minute online self-assessment test. Click here for self-assessment test: https://www.caccusa.org/cs_html/2025_MO-2.pdf. Click here for answer sheet: https://www.caccusa.org/cs_html/2025_MO-2_answer.pdf. Note: $20 material fee will be collected with tuition at registration.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Math Olympiads III (奥数 III)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is designed for gifted middle school students who seek a greater challenge in mathematics and want to prepare for Math Olympiad Division M tests and other prominent middle school mathematics contests. The class will cover number sense &amp; number theory, sequences &amp; series, counting &amp; probability, algebra, and geometry. Students will work on past middle school math contest problems and develop advanced problem-solving skills throughout the class. This class's curriculum corresponds to the material of the National Math Olympiads Division M Contests. Who may enroll: Students at regular school grade levels of 6, 7 and 8, and who were able to score 2 or higher on the 30-minute online self-assessment test. Click here for self-assessment test: https://www.caccusa.org/cs_html/2025_MO-3.pdf. Click here for answer sheet: https://www.caccusa.org/cs_html/2025_MO-3_answer.pdf. Note: $20 material fee will be collected with tuition at registration.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>MATHCOUNTS &amp; MO 4 (初中数学竞赛)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This class is a competitive math class specially designed for advanced middle school students who have successfully completed MO-3 class. With four levels of MATHCOUNTS competition materials - school, chapter, state, and national - the class provides students the extra incentive and perfect atmosphere to push themselves to achieve more in mathematics. The typical homework and class assignments consist of: Sprint Round: This section tests speed and accuracy, allowing 40 minutes to solve 30 problems such that only the most capable students will complete all of the problems. Target Round: This section features multi-step problems that engage students in mathematical reasoning and problem-solving processes. Team Round: This section involves working in groups to develop teamwork strategies. Countdown Round: This section prepares students for the fast-paced, head-to-head competition. The goals of this advanced math class are to help students further developing critical-thinking and problem-solving skills, to motivate and reward them by fostering teamwork and a competitive spirit, and to promote middle school mathematic achievements through fun and challenging MATHCOUNTS problems. The class will be taught in English. Who may enroll: Students at regular school grade levels of 6, 7, and 8, with advanced math level, and who were able to score 15 or higher on the 30-minute online self-assessment test. Click here for self-assessment test: https://www.caccusa.org/cs_html/2025_MC-4.pdf. Click here for answer sheet: https://www.caccusa.org/cs_html/2025_MC-4_answer.pdf. Note: $20 material fee will be collected with tuition at registration. About the teacher: Ms. Qiping Guo graduated from Shanghai Jiao Tong University. She has been teaching competitive mathematics for over 17 years at CACC and various educational centers across the Tri-Valley area. Specializing in Math Olympiads and MATHCOUNTS, Ms. Guo brings a deep passion and enthusiasm to mathematics education. Known for her meticulous organization and thorough preparation, she consistently ensures that her classes are engaging and enriching. Ms. Guo employs customized teaching materials and methods tailored to each student's needs, aiming to instill robust problem-solving skills and an appreciation for the beauty of mathematics. Her students' achievements include numerous perfect scores in MOEMS and AMC8, first-place wins in MATHCOUNTS Chapter competitions, positions on MATHCOUNTS State teams, and qualifications for AIME and the prestigious USAJMO/USAMO. Many of her students continue to excel long after graduating from her classes, gaining admission to highly selective colleges and becoming high achievers in their academic and professional pursuits.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>AMC 8 / AMC 10 - By Teacher Deng &amp; Ms. Willa Lin 由邓老师和林老师执教</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Teacher Deng graduated from the Department of Mathematics of Beijing Normal University with a master's degree in mathematics. He has more than ten years of unique and rich mathematics teaching experience and methods, with a deep understanding of how to teach students to master mathematics knowledge. He is especially good at improving students' mathematics performance and level. Ms. Willa Lin is a highly experienced competitive math teacher based in the Bay Area. She holds a Masters in Computer Science from Syracuse University, New York. With almost a decade of teaching under her belt, her expertise lies in preparing students for Math Kangaroo, AMC 8, and Mathcounts, where she has seen many of her students excel. Ms. Lin's teaching style is known for its effectiveness and adaptability, ensuring that each student receives personalized attention and guidance. Her passion for mathematics education is evident in her dedication to helping students develop strong problem-solving skills and a deep understanding of mathematical concepts. Through her teaching, Ms. Lin inspires her students to embrace the challenges of competitive math and strive for excellence.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>AMC 8 (美国数学竞赛 8, 61课时)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>CACC AMC 8 (American Math Contest) is the first in our series of AMC courses for middle school students up to grade 8. Students should be familiar with pre-algebra and have some understanding of Algebra I and Geometry concepts. Students should have a level of math skills equivalent to a graduated MO Level 3 or CM Level 3 program The class will prepare for the AMC 8 exam in January. The rest of the year will be spent reviewing and further analyzing Algebra/Geometry concepts and studying problems 1-8 from the AMC 10 competition. A successful student is expected to do a considerable amount of homework each week. Courses will be taught in English. What we teach: This course teaches recurring concepts and problem-solving strategies in AMC 8. It mainly focuses on AMC 8 test questions from #10 to #20. Course Structure: The program includes 31 in-person Sunday classes and 30 midweek online homework support sessions, for a total of 61 lessons. To help students rapidly improve their performance and prepare effectively for the AMC 8 competition in January, consistent and focused practice is essential. Students are expected to complete substantial homework to apply the problem-solving strategies taught in class and enhance both speed and accuracy. To support this, we offer a weekly online session led by high school students who have previously achieved outstanding results in the AMC 8. These sessions are designed to review homework problems and answer student questions. The schedule for the online homework tutoring sessions will be announced before the start of the course. Who may enroll: Middle school students up to grade 8, or advanced elementary students who have mastered the concepts of middle school mathematics. Competitive goals: This course focuses on improving AMC 8 exam performance. Note: A materials fee of $20 will be charged along with tuition during registration. Information about teaching materials will be provided in class.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>AMC 10 (美国数学竞赛 10, 61课时)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>CACC AMC 10 (American Math Competition) is a competitive math class. It is specially designed for high school and advanced middle school students who are comfortable with Algebra I and Geometry concepts and successfully completed the CACC AMC 8 class or Mathcounts&amp; MO 4 class. For the first part of the school year, this class will be working on preparation for the AMC 10 math competition at the end of November. Later, the class will focus on deeper understanding of concepts related to the AMC 10 contest as well as the problem solving skills helping students succeed in the competition of the next school year. This class will introduce the students the knowledge and problem solving skills in Number theory, Algebra, Geometry, and Counting and Probability. A successful student is expected to do considerable amount of homework(provided online).The class will be taught in English. What we teach: This class teaches problem solving strategies and math contest taking skills. It focuses mostly on AMC 10 up to question #15. Who may enroll: High school students who are in grade 9 and 10, or middle school students in grade 8 who have mastered the skills taught in AMC 8 class or Mathcounts &amp; MO 4 Class. Course Structure: The program consists of 31 in-person Sunday classes and 30 midweek online homework support sessions, for a total of 61 lessons. To help students make rapid progress within a limited timeframe and prepare thoroughly for the AMC 10 competition in November, consistent and intensive practice is essential. Students are expected to complete substantial homework to apply the problem-solving techniques taught in class, while improving both their speed and accuracy. To support this process, we provide a weekly online session led by high school students who have previously achieved outstanding results in the AMC 10. These sessions focus on explaining homework problems and answering student questions. The schedule for the online homework tutoring sessions will be announced before the start of the course. Competitive goals: AMC 10. This class focuses on improving AMC 10 test scores. Homework: is provided online each week. Note: $20 material fee will be collected with tuition at registration. The information on teaching material will be given in class.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>