<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Badminton Lesson (成人羽毛球训练)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Coach Introduction: Xin Wu is a senior software engineer at IBM and a well-known figure in the Tri-Valley badminton community. He has organized numerous adult badminton tournaments and is always eager to help beginners improve their skills. In addition to his professional work, he also serves as the coach for the Dublin High School badminton team. Under his leadership, the team placed in the top four in the Northern California High School League competitions during the 2023-2024 and 2024-2025 school years. Coach Wu is passionate about helping others and welcomes anyone interested in badminton to join and improve together. Assistant Coach Introduction: Angelina Wu, 16 years old, has been receiving professional badminton training at the Livermore USBA Club since early childhood. She regularly competes in regional and national tournaments and has won multiple titles in her age group in girls' doubles, including championships, runner-up, and third-place finishes. She has also placed in the top four in girls' singles events, gaining extensive practical experience. Angelina will assist in teaching and training during selected classes. Course Content: Basic badminton rules and fundamental techniques. Footwork training, fitness conditioning, and partner drills. Doubles coordination, tactical strategies, and court positioning. Application and practice of offensive and defensive techniques. The class will be held on two courts, with a maximum enrollment of 8 students. This course is designed to help students build a solid foundation in badminton and improve their practical skills. The coach will tailor the content and group activities based on the students' skill levels to ensure that everyone progresses steadily at a pace that suits them. On the last Sundays of the school year, the large gym at Amador High School may be reserved for other events, which could result in the cancellation of two badminton sessions. We will notify you in advance if this occurs. Tuition fees have already been adjusted to account for this possibility.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Club Badminton (成人娱乐羽毛球)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This course provides a space for adults to enjoy recreational badminton and exercise. Please note that no coaching or instruction is provided by the school. According to the Chinese School's full academic year schedule, there are a total of 31 sessions planned for this recreational badminton course. However, on the last Sundays of the school year, the large gym at Amador High School may be reserved for other events, which could result in the cancellation of two badminton sessions. We will notify you in advance if this occurs. Tuition fees have already been adjusted to account for this possibility.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Senior English (老年英语)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>This course is designed to help seniors meet basic communication needs in daily life, such as greeting, self-introduction, shopping, travel, dinning, weather, internet searching, library borrowing, etc. It also helps them understand American culture and local resources in the East Bay area through the environment, community public services, festival activities, etc. Students will learn how to communicate in basic daily English, participate in situational dialogues, group discussions, and share life experiences.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Pop Singing (成人流行音乐歌唱班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Majored in songwriting at Berklee College of Music, Gino Yu is an energetic musician skillful in maintaining energy and delivering excellent performances in front of large audiences. Passionate about coaching and exposing people to diverse musical styles and expressions. Knowledgeable about recording studio equipment and recording procedures. Well-versed in various styles of music. Invited to perform at Fremont Festival of Arts 2019 which held 20,000 audiences. Chosen by the Mayor of Fremont and Citizens for Better Community, performed at Central Park for One World One Community event to celebrate our multiethnic community with 100 musicians from the bay. Winner of the 2021 bay area water cube singing competition.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Chinese Painting for Beginner (成人国画写意花鸟初学者班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Course Overview: This course is specially designed for adult beginners with no prior drawing experience. It offers a step-by-step introduction to the artistic world of traditional Chinese painting. Through a structured study of expressive brush painting (Xieyi) techniques—particularly in flowers and birds—you will experience the beauty of brush and ink, as well as the cultural richness behind the art form. Course Highlights: Learn foundational brush techniques, ink and color application, composition, and expression, gradually mastering the depiction of common subjects such as flowers, plants, birds, and insects. Classic masterpieces by renowned artists will be discussed in class to help sharpen your artistic perspective and aesthetic appreciation. Historical anecdotes and cultural stories will be shared to deepen your understanding and connection with each painting. Small class size with a relaxed, supportive atmosphere. The course is designed to be progressive and enjoyable, promoting both inner peace and artistic enrichment. Who Should Attend: This course is ideal for adult beginners interested in Chinese painting—especially those looking to enhance their artistic sensibility or find a relaxing and meaningful hobby during their free time. Art Supplies: All necessary materials—including Xuan paper, Chinese brushes, ink, and traditional Chinese painting pigments—will be provided. Instructor Bio: Ms. Bella Han graduated from the Industrial Design and Arts Department of Shanghai Jiao Tong University in 1995. She later continued her studies in traditional Chinese painting at the China Academy of Art. Deeply influenced by her father since childhood, she has long been devoted to art education. Bella specializes in fine brush (Gongbi) flower-and-bird painting, as well as sketching, watercolor, and oil painting. To view her artwork: https://sites.google.com/view/bellahan/home.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Drawing (成人绘画)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Adult Drawing is designed for adult students who are interested in learning the fundamentals of drawing in a fun, pressure-free environment. The class covers the principles of design, color theory and various drawing techniques. This is a 1-hr drawing class. THIS CLASS is TAUGHT in Chinese.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Art of Singing Class (成人声乐艺术班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Dang Weiguang is a famous baritone singer and vocal educator. He graduated from Shenyang Conservatory of Music, the Vocal and Opera Department of the Central Conservatory of Music, and the French Vocal Master Class. In 2003, he graduated from the School of Arts of Milliken University in the United States and received an artist diploma. Dang Weiguang won the Excellence Award in the National CC丅V Vocal Competition. He was invited to participate in the Changchun International Film Festival, CCTV, Shanghai Oriental Satellite TV, the opening ceremony of the National University Games and national large-scale cultural performances. He went to Russia to participate in academic exchanges and performances. He has cooperated with the Stanford University Symphony Orchestra, the Chicago Municipal Theater Symphony Orchestra, the San Francisco Opera Symphony Orchestra, the Western Pacific Opera Symphony Orchestra, the Hunan Symphony Orchestra of China, the China Navy Symphony Orchestra, the Shenzhen Symphony Orchestra of China and other orchestras. In Chicago, he was praised by local English newspapers as "a singer with a world-class voice" for starring in "Don Pasquale" and was hailed as the first person to interpret Don Pasquale. He has served as a judge at the Stanford University International Vocal Competition, the Feiyang International Vocal Competition in the United States, the CCTV Young Singer Competition overseas judge, the CCTV "I Want to Go to the Spring Festival Gala" overseas judge, the Chinese Red Song Festival Jiangxi Satellite TV overseas judge, and the Hunan Satellite TV "Happy Boys" overseas judge. He is currently a visiting professor at the Xi'an Conservatory of Music and a visiting professor at Changchun Normal University. He is currently a professor at Ohlone College in California, USA. Vice Chairman of the American Chinese Cultural and Art Alliance. Vocal lessons are divided into three parts: Practice voice, from low to high, from simple to difficult, so as to expand our range and improve our vocal skills and the use of breathing. So that our voice becomes more beautiful and better. In this way, we can sing more songs, songs that we didn't dare to sing before and songs that we couldn't sing before. It will enhance your confidence and ability in singing. Learning songs. After a period of practice, we can sing a song we like, and at the same time, with the help of the teacher, we can find some works that are more suitable for your voice. No matter from the rhythm, language, and emotional expression of the song, there will be different degrees of improvement. Through the study of the second part, you will have a complete grasp of the understanding, appreciation, and processing of the song. So that your own voice will be more pleasant to the ears, and you will change from being timid to being a microphone master. It will also become more confident. Chorus practice. When you have a certain foundation, you need to slowly learn to communicate with others in voice, learn to practice singing with voice parts. Learn to blend with others in voice to complete the work. This course is taught in small classes and in Chinese</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Teacher Wang Linghua 王苓华老师</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The following dance classes are taught by renowned dance artist Linghua Wang: Adult Chinese Dance (成人舞蹈), Basic Skills Training in Dance (舞蹈基本功训练), and The Art of Waist Drum and Handkerchief Dance (腰鼓和红绸舞). Ms. Wang is engaged in the creation, teaching, and performance of Chinese classical folk dance. Her long-term teaching and stage performance experience has cultivated a group of outstanding young dancers. She has developed a unique teaching method by relying on her professional and scientific dance knowledge and skillful use of diversified dance art that combines Chinese and Western dance. Linghua Wang was a member of the Chinese Dancers Association. She graduated with honors from the Shanghai Opera and Dance Theater majoring in dance. He once served as a principal actor in the Shanghai Opera and Dance Theater.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Chinese Dance (成人舞蹈)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Dancing is a comprehensive art, which is closely linked with music, sculpture, painting and other arts. It is graceful body movements as a language which builds up images reflecting the social life. Goals and objectives: training and shaping the image of beauty and self-confidence of the dancers, so that manners and gestures of the dancer can show his or her elegance. Curriculum plan: The first half of the school year will meet the needs of CACC Chinese New Year Gala by preparing and rehearsing different dance programs for the Gala. After the Spring Festival (Chinese New Year) Gala, the course will focus on strengthening physical training, including: basic standing posture, hands position and feet position practice, combined skill exercises in matching breath and action and series of basic skills practice.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Basic Skills Training in Dance (舞蹈基本功训练)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Basic dance skills are the core strength that supports dance performance skills. Basic skills training is to cultivate the accuracy of body movement in an all-round way, including balance, cadence, coordination, rhythm, etc. In dance performances, the grasp of details determines the standard of normal performance, such as the height of the extension of the toe tips, the curvature of the finger bends, the degree of bending when the limbs rotate, etc. Only with solid basic dance skills training can we use our body language to express beauty, deeply portray and create a graceful and characterful dance art image, and convey the emotions and thoughts of dance works. Grasping every detail can increase the expressiveness and charm of dance. This course is suitable for adults aged 18+. Please note: 1. that there will be no classes on November 16, December 7, and December 14. The tuition has been adjusted accordingly. In the event that the instructor needs to take leave due to special circumstances, students will continue their practice under the guidance of the class representative. The school will not provide a substitute teacher during the instructor's absence. 2. Due to limited space at AVHS, this class will be held in a carpeted classroom. Students are asked to follow the instructor's guidance during training.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>The Art of Waist Drum and Handkerchief Dance (腰鼓和红绸舞)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Waist drum is a unique folk large-scale dance art form with a history of more than 2,000 years. The unique and charming waist drum's vigorous and unrestrained dance postures and bold and wild movement changes can exercise the coordination ability of the left and right hands and the left and right brains, improve the quality of rhythm, and understand and master the waist drum through twisting, throwing, shaking and other unrestrained and extraordinary movements. The skills and techniques reflect the inner joy, the graceful posture, and dance steps, and then promote traditional Chinese folk art. Red Silk Dance" is a traditional Han Chinese folk dance, commonly seen in the Yangge performances of the northern Shaanxi region. This dance typically uses red silk ribbons as props, with dancers showcasing their skills and emotions through the flowing movements of the silk. The performance resembles a fiery dragon in motion, where the dancers' agile movements and the ever-changing "fire dragon" create a vibrant display full of youthful energy. This course is suitable for adults aged 18+, recruits students of all genders. Please note: 1. There will be no classes on November 16, December 7, and December 14. The tuition has been adjusted accordingly. In the event that the instructor needs to take leave due to special circumstances, students will continue their practice under the guidance of the class representative. The school will not provide a substitute teacher during the instructor's absence. 2. Due to limited space at AVHS, this class will be held in a carpeted classroom. Students are asked to follow the instructor's guidance during training.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Teacher Li Guoying 李国英老师</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The following dance classes are taught by Li Guoying: Adult Chinese Folk Dance Performance (成人形体民族舞表演班) and Adult Chinese Folk Dance (成人形体民族舞非表演). Teacher Li Guoying has more than 20 years of dance teaching experience, and is particularly good at Yangko, folk dance, Mongolian dance, Tibetan dance and other ethnic dances as well as classical dance and modern body dance. With many years of dance training, stage performance and teaching experience, she has explored a teaching method that is tailored to the individual. The dances that are designed for scholars who love Chinese ethnic and folk dances and incorporate basic skills training are deeply loved by students.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Chinese Folk Dance Performance (成人形体民族舞表演班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The class is focused on participating local performance. The class is designed for performance opportunity at CACC Gala. Chinese Folk Dance class is a combination of health and body shaping benefits while jogging with the fun of dancing. The program has different kinds of folk dancing skills combined into it, though the program is also designed for non-dancers who will be able to keep up and enjoy the class. Students will feel like they are dancing while exercising their bodies and strengthening their cardiovascular systems. This is a class that is fun and enjoyable for both men and women.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Chinese Folk Dance (成人形体民族舞非表演)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The class is designed for those students who are not interested in performing. Chinese Folk Dance class is a combination of health and body shaping benefits while jogging with the fun of dancing. The program has different kinds of folk dancing skills combined into it, though the program is also designed for non-dancers who will be able to keep up and enjoy the class. Students will feel like they are dancing while exercising their bodies and strengthening their cardiovascular systems. This is a class that is fun and enjoyable for both men and women.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Teacher Lily Zhang 理子老师</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The following classes are taught by Lily Zhang: Adult Rhythmic Dance Non-Performance (成人劲舞非表演班) and Adult Rhythmic Dance Performance (成人劲舞表演班). Teacher Lily has more than 20 years of experience as a dance student and performer. She has participated in Chinese dance, Latin dance, jazz dance and many other stage performances throughout the Bay Area. The dance programs she has participated in have won awards at the Taoli Cup Overseas and the WeShine World Dance Competition. She has also taught adult Chinese dance classes at CACC in the past. Her choreographed programs have appeared on the stages of the Spring Festival Gala and Lantern Festival Carnival many times, winning praises from the audience and her students. Noticing a lack of opportunities for Chinese parents to dance for fitness, she created the modern rhythmic dance class to help improve coordination and flexibility while enjoying the joy of movement. In addition, through this course, she wants to create a team of both male and female dancers and perform energetic and exciting dances for the community, showcasing a new image of Chinese Americans! (Men are especially encouraged to sign up!)</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Rhythmic Dance Non-Performance (成人劲舞非表演班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>No matter your gender or prior dance experience, everyone is invited to join CACC's "Adult Rhythmic Dance (Non-Performance) Class" to master energetic and fast-paced moves! This class is all about enjoying the journey—no stage performances required! It's designed to help you master dance rhythm, unwind, stay active, and simply have a great time. This course blends diverse and energetic dance styles like Jazz, Latin, Disco, and Hip-hop, helping participants enhance their posture, boost fitness, explore various movement techniques, and master an array of dance combinations.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Rhythmic Dance Performance (成人劲舞表演班)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Adult Rhythmic Dance Performance Class offers participants the chance to showcase their skills in CACC's Spring Gala and other exciting performances. This course incorporates dynamic dance styles like Jazz, Latin, Disco, and Hip-hop, offering participants the opportunity to enhance posture, boost fitness, and explore diverse movement techniques while mastering dance combinations. Additionally, students will develop skills in stage formations, teamwork, and choreography memorization, all while preparing for performances at CACC's Spring Festival Gala and other exciting events. ** Students in this class need to have some stage performance experience in the past, and can ONLY register with the permission of the teacher. If interested, please contact the school as soon as possible at cs@caccusa.org.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Adult Guitar Play and Sing (成人吉他弹唱班须知)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Majored in songwriting at Berklee College of Music, Gino Yu is an energetic musician skillful in maintaining energy and delivering excellent performances in front of large audiences. Passionate about coaching and exposing people to diverse musical styles and expressions. Knowledgeable about recording studio equipment and recording procedures. Well-versed in various styles of music. Invited to perform at Fremont Festival of Arts 2019 which held 20,000 audiences. Chosen by the Mayor of Fremont and Citizens for Better Community, performed at Central Park for One World One Community event to celebrate our multiethnic community with 100 musicians from the bay. Winner of the 2021 bay area water cube singing competition. In Adult Guitar Play and Sing class, our students will be trained on how to play the instruments with the proper technique and sing while playing the guitar. We will also go over how to learn songs on their own time, thus including some basic music theory on the guitar.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Adult Yoga (瑜伽)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Yoga is a mix of breath control and simple meditation, while holding postures (or asanas) to gain flexibility, strength and an inner peace. It is widely practiced for health, relaxation, and for reducing stress. Our Teachers: Alison and Genny have been practicing yoga for over a decade each, and have a combined decade of teaching experience in the Bay Area and throughout the world. They are both Yoga Alliance 200 Hour Certified and look forward to sharing their passion, knowledge and experience. Either Alison or Tim will teach each week with a class designed for all levels. The class be a typical Vinyasa style, meaning that participants will flow from one posture to the next using their breath. Whether you have practiced yoga in the past, or are brand new to yoga, both teachers will help deepen your practice. This class is designed for 30 weeks for the school year as there might be one week impact due to facility not available. Also, due to this is a new class, there might be some possible unforeseeable changes to be made. The price has reflected on those impacts. This class will be taught in English.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Photography (摄影艺术课程须知)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The purpose of the class is to introduce the artistic knowledge of photography and improve photography skills. The first topic of the photography class called Equipment Selection and Practice includes the introduction of the performance and operations of various lenses and the selection of equipments and camera accessories. The second topic, Artistic Principle of Photography, studies the production process of a photograph. It examines the relationship between art and technique, photographic composition and lighting techniques, and the artistic effect which color produces in a photograph. The last topic of the course, Photography and Production, introduces preproduction technical set-up and theme selection, which includes landscape, portrait, still life, and close-up photography. Post-production discusses traditional film photography and digital rendering and production. The format of the course is interactive. Through using simple language, the course attempts to explain many profound subjects of photography. It will explore the relationship between technique and art, specific technical applications, and the aesthetic application of photography. It endeavors to create a friendly and harmonious classroom environment which is beneficial for students to develop technical skills and achieve artistic accomplishments. The class will be taught primary in Chinese.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>About Tai Chi (太极拳须知)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Tai Chi is a kind of internal martial arts that combines the boxing techniques of many martial arts of past dynasties (mainly Wudang boxing), ancient guiding techniques and breathing techniques, and absorbs traditional Chinese medicine theory to form a kind of internal martial arts that balances yin and yang and cultivates both inside and outside. The theory of yin and yang originated from the natural view of the ancient Chinese people. Everything in the world can be divided into yin and yang. Chinese medicine emphasizes: "When yin prevails, yang will be sick, and when yang prevails, yin will be sick." When practicing Tai Chi, the first thing to do is to compare the human body of the boxer to "Tai Chi". When the body moves, it is divided into yin and yang. Therefore, practicing Tai Chi regularly can balance yin and yang, dredge the meridians, and improve the body's ability to resist disease and recover. In addition to strengthening the body, it also has a strong role in defending against enemies.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Zumba Toning Exercise (尊巴塑身舞)</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The Zumba Toning class is a Latin dance fitness class. Just like walking/jogging to strengthen the leg muscle, this Zumba Toning class is to hold some weights while enjoying Zumba dance to strengthen arm and core muscle. It helps to reduce/get rid of the sag of your arm and your tommy, and have fun with the dance. You may reduce your own workout intensity at the beginning, and gradually work up to the higher intensity level. The class will be taught in both English and Chinese.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>