<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>My child has been studying Chinese language in a different school and just finished Chinese language 2nd grade. We are moving to Pleasanton and plan to enroll him at CACC the upcoming school year - which Chinese class should he sign up in CACC?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Students' Chinese language skills vary, and different language schools may use different materials and progress at different rates. However, if their course material is somewhat comparable to CACC's, your child probably will likely do well in CACC Chinese 3rd grade (either Jinan or Ma Liping track) for the upcoming school year. Generally speaking, if Chinese is a heritage language for the student at home, he/she will likely be fine in Chinese language study grade that is close to his/her regular school class grade. You may also audit the Chinese class during the first two weeks of the school year just to be certain. You can always reach out to school directly for individual concerns.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>For elementary and middle school Chinese, CACC appears to offer two tracks: Jinan University and Ma Liping. What's the difference between them and how should I choose?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The two tracks are designed with different teaching methodologies in mind, and parents can choose either one based on their preference. As long as students put in solid efforts, either track will prepare them for long term success in Chinese learning. In terms of teaching methodology, Ma Liping Chinese does not teach pinyin until 3rd grade and places higher priority on reading than writing,allowing students to learn larger vocabulary in the process. On the other hand, Jinan Chinese teaches pinyin starting from 1st grade and puts more emphasis on writing, with students spending a bit less time reading Chinese text. Note that textbook fee is already included in tuition for JinanChinese, but parents need to buy Ma Liping textbook separately. For more details about the textbook used in thetwo tracks please refer to: https://www.caccusa.org/info.php?p=2</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Do students need to take a placement test if they want to enroll in high school Chinese at CACC?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>For high school Chinese we have a for-credit track and a not-for-credit track. There are three classes in the for-credit track (Chinese III, IV, AP) and you need to take a placement test at the end of March to determine the appropriate class to take for the upcoming school year. There are two classes in the not-for-credit track (high school Chinese prep, and AP prep) and you don't need to take a placement test for either of those. Both the for-credit AP class and the not-for-credit AP prep class are designed to prepare the student for the AP test in May. The for-credit class is four hours per week compared to two hours for the not-for-credit class. For more details please visit https://www.caccusa.org/program.php?p=10</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Can you share a sample placement test for me to study?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>The placement test is meant to assess students' Chinese level so that they enroll in a class that's most suitable for them to study in right now, and to move into AP class only when they are ready (that will likely result in a successful outcome in the eventual AP test). The placement test is designed to assess students' level rather than serving as a teaching tool, and cannot be distributed.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>My child has finished 8th grade Chinese and did well. Does he qualify for AP class?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>It depends. Some students have reached the aptitude and maturity required for the AP class after a successful 8th grade study, but most have not. The best way to objectively find out about his actual level is through a placement test. Other than a few students who may be ready to go directly into AP class after 8th grade, most students will benefit from taking Chinese III or IV class first before taking AP class, and will more likely achieve the desired score in the eventual AP test.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>