<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>School Information</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Location: Amador Valley High School at 1155 Santa Rita Road, Pleasanton, CA 94566</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Open: 9:00AM - 12:50PM every Sunday from 08/17/2025 to 05/17/2026, excluding holidays and breaks (view Calendar)</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Office: Room Q215</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Email Contact: cs@caccusa.org</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Mailing Address: CACC, PO Box 12028, Pleasanton, CA 94588</category>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Registration Basics</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Please use one account per family. Students living in the same household are counted as one family. There is a $50 fine for violating this rule.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Registration Starting Dates</category>
                    <category_example>05/03/2025: Priority Registration (for current school year teachers, room parents, BOD, retired BOD, and CS staff)</category_example>
                    <category_example>05/09/2025: Regular Registration (for all currently enrolled students)</category_example>
                    <category_example>05/16/2025: Public Registration (for all returning and new students)</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Last Registration Dates</category>
                    <category_example>09/04/2025: all High School Chinese and AP Prep classes</category_example>
                    <category_example>10/31/2025: all Chinese Language classes</category_example>
                    <category_example>12/31/2025: all except Spring classes</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Before proceeding with registration, you may want to read Registration FAQ.</category>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Tuition and Fees</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Registration Fee</category>
                    <category_example>$30 non-refundable per account each school year.</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Tuition</category>
                    <category_example>Discounted tuition must be paid in full before 07/01/2025.</category_example>
                    <category_example>Starting from 07/01/2025, tuition is at a regular price.</category_example>
                    <category_example>Before 01/01/2026, full tuition</category_example>
                    <category_example>Starting from 01/01/2026, 60% of the tuition for full year class</category_example>
                    <category_example>Starting from 03/01/2026, 40% of the tuition for full year class</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Service Deposit</category>
                    <category_example>$50 per account, refundable. See Yard Duty FAQ for details.</category_example>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Payment Method</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Zelle: This is the preferred payment method to save CACC's operation costs.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>PayPal: Online payment is quick and secure. A 2.5% transaction fee will be charged.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Personal Check: Make it payable to CACC.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>During the summer</category>
                    <category_example>Mail to PO Box 12028, Pleasanton, CA 94588</category_example>
                    <category_example>Checks are collected once a week. There may be a delay in updating your online account, and a possibility that your class be filled before processing your check.</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>During the school year</category>
                    <category_example>Checks can be delivered in-person to the school office every working Sunday starting 08/17/2025. The early bird discount will not be honored as it passes 07/01/2025.</category_example>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Class Observation</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Classes open to all students / parents in the first two weeks. No permission is required.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Starting from the third week, one-time class try-out is permitted for one student per class. Please obtain the Observation Slip from the office.</category>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Class Change Policy</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>On or before 09/04/2025</category>
                    <category_example>You can change class yourself.</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>After 09/04/2025</category>
                    <category_example>Any class change must be handled in the office.</category_example>
                    <category_example>No refund or class credit for any remaining balance as a result of class change.</category_example>
                    <category_example>Each class change will be subject to a $20 processing fee.</category_example>
                    <category_example>In addition to the $20 fee, if switching to a class with higher tuition, the tuition difference must be paid.</category_example>
                    <category_example>If a class is paid before 07/01/2025 and needs to be switched to another class after 09/04/2025, a difference between the discounted and regular tuition must be paid.</category_example>
                    <category_example>Explain to the office why you don't like the class (the school might find a way to help you stay in this class)</category_example>
                    <category_example>Discuss with the office for other alternatives</category_example>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Refund Policy</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>On or before 08/17/2025</category>
                    <category_example>100% tuition refund, except registration fee and textbook fee described below.</category_example>
                    <category_example>For a class that includes textbook fee in the tuition, such as PK-, K- and C-</category_example>
                    <category_example>The textbook fee will normally be deducted</category_example>
                    <category_example>This amount is refundable only if the textbook can be returned in original condition</category_example>
                    <category_example>Return the textbook to the office if the fee is refundable</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Between 08/18/2025 and 09/04/2025</category>
                    <category_example>5% refund processing fee, in addition to the fee(s) stated above, regardless of the number of classes attended.</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>After 09/04/2025</category>
                    <category_example>No refund will be allowed whether you have attended the class or not.</category_example>
                    <category_example>Due to student medical condition with doctor's written approval, or moved out of 50-mile radius with proof</category_example>
                    <category_example>A refund is allowed.</category_example>
                    <category_example>The refund amount will be prorated based on the date provided on the doctor's note, or the family moving date. There will be a 5% charge to cover the process cost.</category_example>
                    <category_example>The medical leave refund applies to the student only, no other family members' medical reasons are accepted.</category_example>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Refund Process</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Refund process will start in October.</category>
                    <category_example>The refund will be sent to the original Zelle or PayPal account where the payment was made</category_example>
                    <category_example>Refund for check payment will be issued with a check refund</category_example>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>For payment made by PayPal:</category>
                    <category_example>If there is any loss due to change of your PayPal account, and CACC Chinese School is not notified, it is your responsibility to resolve the issue with PayPal. CACC Chinese School will not re-issue a refund without conclusive evidence that the refund has not been received.</category_example>
                    <category_example>DO NOT CANCEL your payment through your PayPal account. There will be a $100 penalty charged by CACC Chinese School to cover fees and costs associated with your cancellation. If you fail to pay this penalty, CACC reserves the right to refuse your future participation and registration in any CACC event or its Chinese School class.</category_example>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Minimum Age, Class Size, and Cancellation</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>The minimum age for students attending PK class is based on student's birthday on or before 09/01/2021.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>The minimum age for students attending any enrichment class is based on student's birthday on or before 09/01/2020.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>The minimum age for students attending Sports Classes varies. Please check for specific Sports Class age limits.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Some classes have different age requirements due to the nature of the class setting. Please refer to the specific class description.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Class size is decided by the school. The school reserves the right to change or cancel classes without prior notice. Applicable refunds will be issued due to these special circumstances.</category>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Teacher Change and Related Refund Policy</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>The school reserves the right to change teachers without prior notice.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>The refund policy remains the same, regardless of teacher changes.</category>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Child and Dependent Care Expenses</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>CACC Chinese School is a school-based enrichment program provider. Regardless of your work arrangement, its tuition is not eligible for the tax deduction.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Yard Duty Policy</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>CACC Chinese School requires each family to carry out 2 to 4 hours of school assigned duties per school year. Please visit Yard Duty Policy and Yard Duty FAQ for details.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Questions or Concerns</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_list>
                <list_item>
                    <category>Answers to many questions can be found in FAQ.</category>
                </list_item>
                <list_item>
                    <category>For other questions, concerns, or assistance, please email us.</category>
                </list_item>
            </answer_list>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>