<frequently_asked_questions>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>How do I open an account with CACC?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_steps>
                <step>Go to the CACC home page: www.caccusa.org.</step>
                <step>Click Login tab.</step>
                <step>Click Create New Account.</step>
            </answer_steps>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>What if I forget my password?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>After clicking on the Login tab, click on Recover my password, then enter your username and email address. Your password will be emailed to you. If you have trouble in getting your password this way, please email to cs@caccusa.org.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>What if I forget my username?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>After clicking on the Login tab, click on Retrieve my username, then enter your email address, phone number and your full name. Your username will be emailed to you. If you have trouble in getting your username this way, please send an email to cs@caccusa.org with your email and phone number to request your username. Your username will be sent to you within 24hrs. *** Please DO NOT open a new account to avoid confusion and trouble down the line.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>How do I change my password?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Click on My Profile then Account, fill in the current password, new password, confirm password and click on Save at the bottom.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>Can I change my email address?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Yes. But, you have to do BOTH the followings after logging into your account:</answer_text>
            <answer_steps>
                <step>Click on My Profile then Account, fill your new email address, as well as other profile information, including mailing address. You must put in current password, then click on Save to save all the changes. - The email address provided here is mainly used for receiving emails from CACC and CACC Chinese School.</step>
                <step>Click on Contact and update 1st and 2nd Guardian's emails, if applicable - The email address provided here is mainly used for teacher contact and class information.</step>
            </answer_steps>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
    <question_and_answer>
        <question>How do I change my profile?</question>
        <answer>
            <answer_text>Your profile information are stored in CACC's database after you have registered. You can change all of them except your username. Please click on My Profile and Account, Guardian, Emergency Contact or Student tab to make changes, then click Save at the bottom to save your changes.</answer_text>
        </answer>
    </question_and_answer>
</frequently_asked_questions>